export const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1514888286974-6c03e2ca1dba?w=800&auto=format&fit=crop",
    correctAnswer: "kucing",
    options: ["kucin", "kucing", "kucim", "kacin"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1583337130417-3346a1be7dee?w=800&auto=format&fit=crop",
    correctAnswer: "anjing",
    options: ["anjeng", "anjing", "anying", "ajing"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1628522331661-505646eede3a?q=80&w=870&auto=format&fit=crop",
    correctAnswer: "ayam",
    options: ["ayem", "ayam", "ayim", "ayom"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    image: "https://plus.unsplash.com/premium_photo-1661888759779-b10085f08972?q=80&w=864&auto=format&fit=crop",
    correctAnswer: "gajah",
    options: ["gajah", "gaja", "gojah", "gejah"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    image: "https://plus.unsplash.com/premium_photo-1664302688826-1521c027c8f8?q=80&w=2964&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D",
    correctAnswer: "singa",
    options: ["singa", "singo", "singe", "singah"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    image: "https://plus.unsplash.com/premium_photo-1667155652500-aa666676fa39?q=80&w=2942&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D",
    correctAnswer: "kelinci",
    options: ["kelinci", "kalinci", "kelincu", "kelince"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    image: "https://plus.unsplash.com/premium_photo-1664362416559-0cdc66f49cf3?q=80&w=2940&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D",
    correctAnswer: "kuda",
    options: ["kuda", "kude", "kudo", "kudah"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1708321173120-963f1c4b6d64?q=80&w=2940&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D",
    correctAnswer: "burung",
    options: ["burung", "bureng", "burong", "burang"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    image: "https://plus.unsplash.com/premium_photo-1722908885987-628cef023cc9?q=80&w=3132&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D",
    correctAnswer: "ikan",
    options: ["ikan", "ikun", "iken", "ikon"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1556596187-c3d988ea368c?q=80&w=3173&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D",
    correctAnswer: "bebek",
    options: ["bebek", "bebak", "bebik", "bebok"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1621948939774-82376a8ce2eb?q=80&w=2940&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D",
    correctAnswer: "kambing",
    options: ["kambing", "kambeng", "kembing", "kombing"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1635504931620-2b5d3edf0598?q=80&w=2942&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D",
    correctAnswer: "sapi",
    options: ["sapi", "sape", "sapu", "sipo"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    image: "https://plus.unsplash.com/premium_photo-1675269270967-6c00cc672b85?q=80&w=2944&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D",
    correctAnswer: "monyet",
    options: ["monyet", "monyot", "munyet", "manyet"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1485735662814-c4f66e49dbae?q=80&w=2940&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D",
    correctAnswer: "jerapah",
    options: ["jerapah", "jerapoh", "jirapah", "jurapah"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1615963244664-5b845b2025ee?q=80&w=2636&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D",
    correctAnswer: "harimau",
    options: ["harimau", "harimou", "herimau", "horimau"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1526319238109-524eecb9b913?q=80&w=2924&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D",
    correctAnswer: "zebra",
    options: ["zebra", "zebro", "zibra", "zabra"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1638704957265-0817f29d9b6b?q=80&w=2940&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D",
    correctAnswer: "pinguin",
    options: ["pinguin", "penguin", "pingun", "pengun"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1642403944864-04ad7f092eff?q=80&w=2940&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D",
    correctAnswer: "angsa",
    options: ["angsa", "angso", "angsu", "angsi"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1637017965090-6ae81b4575d0?q=80&w=2940&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D",
    correctAnswer: "kerbau",
    options: ["kerbau", "kerbou", "karbau", "korbau"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1564349683136-77e08dba1ef7?w=800&auto=format&fit=crop",
    correctAnswer: "panda",
    options: ["panda", "pando", "pandu", "pandi"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1559253664-ca249d4608c6?w=800&auto=format&fit=crop",
    correctAnswer: "katak",
    options: ["kata", "katag", "katak", "ketek"],
    question: "Hewan apakah ini?"
  },
];